(Music)
(موسيقى)
♫ I don't understand myself, ♫
♫أنا لا أفهم♫
♫ why they keep talking of love, ♫
♫لماذا يتحدثون دوماً عن الحب ♫
♫ if they come near me, ♫
♫عندما يقتربون مني♫
♫ if they look into my eyes and kiss my hand. ♫
♫عندما يحدقون في عيني و يلثمون يدي♫
♫ I don't understand myself, ♫
♫أنا لا أفهمهم♫
♫ why they talk of magic, ♫
♫لماذا يتحدثون عن السحر ♫
♫ that no one withstands, ♫
♫لا شيء يمكن ان يصمد♫
♫ if he sees me, if he passes by. ♫
♫إن رآني أحدهم .. أو مر بقربي ♫
♫ But if the red light is on ♫
♫ولكن عندما يشتعل النور الاحمر♫
♫ in the middle of the night ♫
♫في منتصف الليل♫
♫ and everybody listens to my song, ♫
♫والجميع يستمع لأغانيَّ♫
♫ then it is plain to see. ♫
♫فمن السهل أن ترى♫
♫ My lips, they give so fiery a kiss, ♫
♫شفتي .. فهما تقبلان بشغف♫
♫ my limbs, they are supple and soft. ♫
♫أطرافي .. بيضاء وخفيفة ♫
♫ It is written for me in the stars, ♫
♫مكتوب لي في السماء بالنجوم♫
♫ thou shalt kiss, thou shalt love. ♫
♫أنت قبلة تندثر .. أنت حب يندثر♫
♫ My feet, they glide and float, ♫
♫قدمي تطفو و تسبح♫
♫ my eyes, they lure and glow. ♫
♫عيني تتألق و تنير♫
♫ And I dance as if entranced, 'cause I know, ♫
♫وأنا أرقص رقصة الدخول لأني أعلم♫
♫ my lips give so fiery a kiss. ♫
♫شفتي تقبل بكل صدق♫
♫ In my veins, ♫
♫في عروقي ♫
♫ runs a dancer's blood, ♫
♫يجري دمُ راقص ♫
♫ because my beautiful mother ♫
♫بسبب والدتي الجميلة♫
♫ was the Queen of dance ♫
♫والتي كانت ملكة الرقص♫
♫ in the gilded Alcazar. ♫
♫ترتدي حلة رقص مذهبة♫
♫ She was so very beautiful, ♫
♫لقد كانت جميلة جداً ♫
♫ I often saw her in my dreams. ♫
♫أنا اصادفها حينا في أحلامي ♫
♫ If she beat the tambourine ♫
♫إن عزفت على الدف ♫
♫ to her beguiling dance, all eyes were glowing admiringly. ♫
♫وبدأت تتمايل في الرقص .. كل العيون تتوهج♫
♫ She reawakened in me, ♫
♫إنها تقطن في نفسي♫
♫ mine is the same lot. ♫
♫روحي تشبه روحها ♫
♫ I dance like her at midnight ♫
♫أنا أرقص مثلها في منتصف الليل♫
♫ and from deep within I feel: ♫
♫وفي داخلي أشعر ♫
♫ My lips, they give so fiery a kiss, ♫
♫أن شفتي ستقبل بشغف وحب ♫
♫ my limbs, they are supple and soft. ♫
♫أطرافي .. بيضاء وخفيفة ♫
♫ It is written for me in the stars, ♫
♫مكتوب في السماء بواسطة النجوم♫
♫ thou shalt kiss, thou shalt love. ♫
♫أنت قبلة تندثر .. أنت حب يندثر♫
♫ And I dance as if entranced, 'cause I know, ♫
♫وأنا أرقص رقصة الدخول لأني أعلم♫
♫ my lips give so fiery a kiss. ♫
♫شفتي تقبل بكل صدق♫
(Applause)
(تصفيق)